[
    
    {
            
        "question": "three consecutive integers add up to 303 what is the small integer?",
        "a": "97",
        "b": "99",
        "c": "100",
        "d": "102",
        "correct": "2"
    },

    {
        
        "question": "what is the next number in series  1 , 3 , 6 , 10 ?",
        "a": "12",
        "b": "13",
        "c": "14",
        "d": "15",
        "correct": "3"
    },

    {
        
        "question": "If the day befor yesterday is Wednesday , what day will it be 2 days befor tomorrow?",
        "a": "Tuesday",
        "b": "Wednesday",
        "c": "Thursday",
        "d": "Friday",
        "correct": "2"
        },
    {
    
        "question": "If it's 2:30 PM what time will be it in 108 hours?",
        "a": "2:30 AM",
        "b": "11:30 PM",
        "c": "1:25 AM",
        "d": "none ",
        "correct": "0"
        },

    {
        
        "question": "1 + 2 + 3 + 4 + 5 + ... +50 ?",
        "a": "915",
        "b": "1000",
        "c": "5521",
        "d": "1275",

        "correct": "3"
    },




    {
        "question": "I ______ bus on Mondays.",
        "a": "'m going to work with",
        "b": "'m going to work by",
        "c": "go to work with",
        "d": "go to work by",

        "correct": "3"
    },

    {
        "question": "I ______ to the cinema.",
        "a": "not usually go",
        "b": "don't usually go",
        "c": "don't go usually",
        "d": "do not go usually",

        "correct": "1"
    },

    {
        "question": "We went to the market ______ some vegetables.",
        "a": "to buy",
        "b": "for buy",
        "c": "for to buy",
        "d": "for buying",

        "correct": "0"
    },

    {
        "question": "I couldn't eat ______ before the exam.",
        "a": "anything",
        "b": "nothing",
        "c": "everything",
        "d": "something",

        "correct": "0"
    },

    {
        "question": "I'll call you when I ______ home.",
        "a": "'m going to arrive",
        "b": "arrive",
        "c": "will arrive",
        "d": "arrived",


        "correct": "1"
    },






    {
        "question": "In Html one of below element is block element",
        "a": "<span>",
        "b": "<a>",
        "c": "<img>",
        "d": "<p>",

        "correct": "3"
    },

    {
        "question": "which tage in Html using to make conect with external Cascading Style Sheets ",
        "a": "link",
        "b": "src",
        "c": "href",
        "d": "a",

        "correct": "0"
    },

    {
        "question": "one of below is id ",
        "a": ".selector",
        "b": "$selector",
        "c": "#selector",
        "d": "selector",

        "correct": "2"
    },

    {
        "question": "media query type :",
        "a": "screen",
        "b": "normal",
        "c": "print",
        "d": "a + c",

        "correct": "3"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
        "a": "parse()",
        "b": "stringify()",
        "c": "toString()",
        "d": "none",

        "correct": "1"
    },

    {
        "question": " a = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]; console.log(a.slice(2, 4));\n the resulut in console will be  ",
        "a": "3 , 4",
        "b": "2 , 3 ",
        "c": "1 , 4 , 5",
        "d": "2 , 3 , 4",

        "correct": "0"
    },

    {
        "question": "What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
        "a": "setTimeout",
        "b": "await",
        "c": "async",
        "d": "function",

        "correct": "2"
    },

    {
        "question": "What are all the types of Pop up boxes available in JavaScript?",
        "a": "Alert",
        "b": "Confirm and",
        "c": "Prompt",
        "d": "All",

        "correct": "2"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which JavaScript method is used to access an HTML element by id?",
        "a": "getElement(id)",
        "b": "getElementById()",
        "c": "elementById(id)",
        "d": "getElementById(id)",

        "correct": "3"
    },

    {
        "question": "JavaScript objects are written with ",
        "a": "round brackets ()",
        "b": "curly brackets {}",
        "c": "square brackets []",
        "d": "double quotes ",

        "correct": "1"
    }




]